(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
#OmaruPolkaBirthday2026
新曲のお披露目あり！
New song reveal!
Glitter of Love
1/30 21:00~
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト10名
Polka's live with the most guests ever: 10 Hololive members
Glitter of Love
遥か空 響いてる
Resonating in the distant sky,
祈りは
my prayer
奇跡に
turns into a miracle.
ETERNAL BLAZE
作詞：水樹奈々 / 作曲：上松範康 (Elements Garden)
Lyrics: Nana Mizuki / Composition: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
真っ赤な 碧に 溶けて
Dissolving into the deep crimson blue,
流れてく 涙の 粒
teardrops flow away.
迷いなく 包み込む ぬくもりに 出会った
I encountered a warmth that envelops me without hesitation.
真っ白な 雪のように
Like pure white snow,
どこまでも 素直な 言葉
words that are honest through and through,
鉄の 羽 纏った 僕を 動かしてく
move me, clad in wings of steel.
傷つく たび 優しく なれる
Each time I'm hurt, I can become kinder.
君の その 笑顔だけ 守り抜きたい 願いは ひとつ
I have but one wish: to protect your smile until the end.
時を 超え 刻まれた 悲しみの 記憶
Memories of sadness carved across time,
まっすぐに 受け止める 君は 光の 騎士
you face them head-on, a warrior of light.
あの日 胸に 灯った 永遠の 炎
The eternal flame that was lit in my heart that day,
深い 闇 解き放って 自由の 扉 開いてく
release the deep darkness and open the door to freedom.
強く 果てない 未来へ
To a strong and endless future.
向かい風の 月に
By the moon in the headwind,
映し出す 心の 影
the shadows of the heart are projected.
寂しげに つぶやいた
You whispered lonely words,
君の そばに いたい
I want to be by your side.
真実と 向き合うこと
Facing the truth,
教えてくれた 勇気は
the courage you taught me
僕を 駆け巡って
courses through me,
夢に 目覚めてゆく
waking up to the dream.
触れ合う 気持ち 離れないように しっかりと 抱きしめて
Holding these shared feelings tight, so we never drift apart,
確かな 想い 貫いてゆく
I will see these certain feelings through.
銀の 海に 隠した
Hidden in the silver sea,
空白の ページ
a blank page.
君だけが 知っている
Only you know,
本当の 僕を見せて
so show me the true me.
吹き荒れる 刹那さに
Amidst the raging sorrow,
生まれゆく 誓い
a vow is being born.
もう 何も 怖くないよ
I'm not afraid of anything anymore.
結んだ 視線 そらさずに
Without averting our locked gaze,
大切な 今を 始める
let's begin this precious 'now'.
君が 君で いられる場所
The place where you can be yourself,
幻に させないように
I won't let it become a mere illusion.
消えない 雨の 苦しみも
Even the pain of the unceasing rain,
鍵を 壊して ぶつけてよ
break the lock and throw it all at me.
隣に いるから
Because I'm right here beside you,
すべてを 信じて
believe in everything.
時を 超え 刻まれた 悲しみの 記憶
Memories of sadness carved across time,
まっすぐに 受け止める 君は 光の 騎士
you face them head-on, a warrior of light.
あの日 胸に 灯った 永遠の 炎
The eternal flame that was lit in my heart that day,
深い 闇 解き放って
release the deep darkness...
研ぎ澄まして
Sharpen your senses
自由の扉
The door to freedom
開いてく
Is opening up
強く果てない
To a strong, endless
未来へ
Future
そう、きっとここから
Yes, surely from here
始まる
It begins
お待たせみんなー！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
今年もポルカの誕生日が始まったー！
Polka's birthday has begun again this year!
タイトルは、かっこいい「Glitter of Love」ということで
The title is the cool "Glitter of Love," and...
ハッシュタグはこちら！
Here's the hashtag!
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026 で
Use #OmaruPolkaBirthday2026 and...
いーっぱい、いーっぱい呟いてねー！
...tweet lots and lots!
はーい！
Alright!
いや、今回はテーマがまず、愛と勇気と戦う女の子になってます。
Well, first off, the theme this time is girls who fight with love and courage.
そして見てくださいこのステージ！
And look at this stage!
えい！ほー！すごい広い！
Hah! Whoa! It's so huge!
おおー！なんとですね、広いんですけれども
Oh! It's actually quite spacious, but...
まずスクリーンが超デカい！大迫力！
First of all, the screen is super big! Great impact!
なんとなんと、いつもの3倍くらい頑張りました。
It's actually, like, three times the effort of usual.
いや、頑張ってもらいました。
Well, they worked hard for me.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
というわけでですね、ここからゲストの方々が
And so, from here on, we'll have many guests...
たくさんいらっしゃいます！
...coming on!
もうホロメンだけなら多分
Just counting Hololive members, I think it's...
尾丸ポルカ史上最多のゲスト数だと思っております！
...the most guests in Omaru Polka history!
それをね、これからノンストップでお送りするので
We'll be bringing them to you non-stop...
楽しんでいってください！
...so please enjoy!
というわけで、いくぞー！
Alright then, here we go!
遺伝子レベルの　INDIPENDENCE
Independence at the genetic level
絶望も希望も　抱いて
Embracing both despair and hope
贖え　命尽きるまで
Redeem yourself until life's end
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Seiten Galaxy Cross
光と飛沫のキス
A kiss of light and spray
恋のような
Like a love
虹のバースデー
A rainbow birthday
どんな美しき日も
No matter how beautiful the day
何か生まれ
Something is born
何かが死ぬ
Something dies
せめて歌おう I LOVE YOU
At least let's sing "I LOVE YOU"
世界が酷い地獄だとしても
Even if the world is a terrible hell
せめて伝えよう I LOVE YOU
At least let's convey "I LOVE YOU"
解放の時は来た
The time for liberation has come
星降る天へと響き跳べ RE-BIRTHDAY SONG
Echo and leap to the star-filled heavens, RE-BIRTHDAY SONG
スターダスト
Stardust
そして奇跡は待つものじゃなくて
And miracles aren't things to wait for
その手で作るものと吠えろ
Howl that they are things made with those hands
涙した過去の苦みをレクイエムにして
Turning the bitterness of the tearful past into a requiem
正真正銘 全力で
With all our might, honestly
輝け FUTUREは
Shine, the future
信じて鳴らせ 星天ギャラクシィ
Believe and let it ring, Galaxy Cross
一人じゃないことを
That you're not alone
やがて君は 知る日のため
For the day you will eventually know
指先伝わる熱を
The heat transmitted from the fingertips
分かち合って 明日に向かう
Sharing it and heading for tomorrow
永遠なる空に I FEEL YOU
To the eternal sky, I FEEL YOU
自由の魂は 孤高にせましない
A free soul doesn't care about solitude
不滅なる夢に I FEEL YOU
In the immortal dream, I FEEL YOU
魂へと手を握れ
Hold hands with the soul
運命も宿命も断ち切る力で
With the power to cut through fate and destiny
そして重なった夢
And the overlapping dreams
…抜き 煌めき
...shining bright,
十字となって闇を暴く
Becoming a cross and exposing the darkness.
駆け抜けたあの丘には
On that hill we ran through,
神様も知らない
even God doesn't know
歴史が光り誇る
a history that shines with pride.
My top and brave heart!
この絆
This bond,
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Seiten Galaxy Cross!
Try! Try! Trio Dreams!
Let's Sing! Let's Swing! Let's Dance!
Let's Born! Let's Smile! Let's Fly!
Uuu... be a girl!
Let's Sing! Let's Swing! Let's Dance!
Let's Born! Let's Smile! Let's Fly!
ときめき 出会いで 変わってく 世界 未来
A world and future that changes
with heart-pounding encounters.
1+1+1は無限
1+1+1 is infinity.
唇からこぼれる歌は
The song spilling from our lips is...
La la la...
プリズム 眩しい光サンシャイン
Prism, dazzling light, sunshine.
3人寄れば ほら 最高！
When the three of us get together, it's the best!
始まる 叩いて 扉
It's starting, knock on the door.
Like Enjoy Together
ときめき止まらない
The excitement doesn't stop.
Humming! (Whoo!)
Just OK! (Fu!)
Chance of! (Way!)
Respond! (Ready!)
輝くプリズムのように
Like a shining prism.
好きな 好きな フレーズを
My favorite, favorite phrases.
心音符に 夢を乗せて
Put your dreams on the notes of your heart.
君に あなたのもとへ
To you, to your side.
今宵 もっともっと 輝きあえるね
Tonight we can shine even more together.
みんな
Everyone!
瞳づくりに いつだって 笑顔 映し合おう
Let's always reflect our smiles
in each other's eyes.
噛みしめて
Savor it.
君がいるから パワー生まれるよ 今日も
Power is born because you are here today too.
Try! Try! Trio Dreams!
Let's Sing! Let's Swing! Let's Dance!
Let's Born! Let's Smile! Let's Fly!
Uuu... be a girl!
Let's Sing! Let's Swing! Let's Dance!
Let's Born! Let's Smile! Let's Fly!
一緒だったから 感じる ハッピー
Feeling happy because we were together.
1×1×1は無敵
1x1x1 is invincible.
出し惜しみはなしで 全部あげたい
I want to give everything
without holding back.
ハプニング さえも 超絶 Wonderful
Even happenings are super wonderful.
3人寄れば 文殊の知恵
Three heads are better than one.
見せるよ きっと 伝説の Like Encore 情熱
We'll show you the legendary passion,
like an encore!
You feel me too (Humming!)
Hot and pop (Just OK!)
Chance of! (Can zone!)
Respond! (Welcome!)
カテゴリライズいらないね
No need for categorization.
好きな 好きな...
Favorite, favorite...
思い切り シンフォニー
A symphony with all our might!
羽広げ ハートの奥の奥へ
Spreading wings, deep into
the depths of the heart.
命は 輝きで できて いるの
Life is made of brilliance.
Yes! Yes!
ビッグスクリーンも はみ出しちゃう 嬉しい 楽しい
It spills out of the big screen,
happy and fun.
君を知って 知らない 自分に 会えたよ
Knowing you, I met a version of myself
I didn't know.
Try! Try! Trio Dreams!
やったー！
Yay!
瞳スクリーニング いつまでも 笑顔写し合おうか",
Eyes screening, let's keep reflecting our smiles forever,
君がいるからパワー生まれるよ 今日も",
because you are here, power is born today too.
Tri Tri Trio!!
Let's Sing, Let's Swing, Let's Dance, Let's Burn, Let's Smile, Let's Fly Woo Free-Show!!
Let's Sing, Let's Swing, Let's Dance, Let's Burn, Let's Smile, Let's Fly Woooo!!
Awakening Harmony
作詞：こだまさおり 作曲：脇眞富
Lyrics: Saori Kodama, Composition: Masatomi Waki
暗闇の真ん中
In the center of darkness,
まっすぐな眼差し
a straightforward gaze.
立ち上がる姿
Your figure standing up,
ちゃんと見ていたよ
I was watching it properly.
閉じ込められそうな
Seemingly trapped,
心を奮い立たせ
stirring up the heart,
収まりきらない
uncontainable,
輝きを放ち
emitting a brilliance.
射抜かれた胸の奥
Deep in the pierced chest,
泣きついたまま叫ぶ
screaming while clinging on.
それだけでも
Even just with that,
自由になれる 待っていて
I can become free, please wait for me.
取り戻したい
I want to take back
光の世界
the world of light.
その笑顔 勇気 涙
That smile, courage, and tears,
夢 希望の兆し
the signs of dreams and hope.
君と明日を
Wishing for tomorrow with you,
願う内から生まれる
it's born from within.
私たちのハーモニー
Our harmony
君へ
to you.
それでも暗闇は
Even so, darkness
訪れてしまうもの
is something that will visit.
惑わされない
Don't be led astray,
君は君だから
because you are you.
私会えた日々が
The days I was able to meet you
心を輝かせてる
are making my heart shine.
一人じゃないこと
That I'm not alone,
気づかせてくれた
you made me realize.
抱えきれぬほどの
Instead of the 'thank you'
ありがとうの代わりに
that is more than I can carry,
鍵をかけて 一つになる
lock it up and become one.
受け止めて
Accept it.
取り戻すんだ
I'm going to take back
光の未来
the future of light.
今 熱い思い 繋ごう
Now, let's connect our passionate feelings.
叶えに行くよ
I'm going to make it come true.
君と一緒に
Together with you,
願える奇跡 重ねて
layering the miracles we can wish for.
広がっていくハーモニー
The spreading harmony.
目覚める時が来たね
The time to wake up has come.
本当の自分になる
I'll become my true self.
満ちる 運命
A fulfilling fate.
取り戻したい
I want to take back
光の世界
the world of light.
その笑顔 勇気 涙
That smile, courage, and tears,
夢 希望の兆し
the signs of dreams and hope.
君と明日を
Wishing for tomorrow with you,
願う内から生まれる
it's born from within.
私たちのハーモニー
Our harmony
君へ
to you.
トライアングル・ドリーマー
作詞・作曲：村カワ基成
Triangle Dreamer
Lyrics/Composition: Motonari Murakawa
デイ・バイ・デイ 日に日に 募るの 乙女心
Day by day, day by day, a maiden's heart grows.
同じ
Same
いつものクラス　ナナメ前
In our usual class, diagonally in front of me
おとなしい君
The quiet you
さっそうと現れた
Appeared so gallantly
だけどやさしい
But you're also kind
いつも頼れる彼
He's someone I can always rely on
放課後　恋愛相談の
After school, from a consultation about love
帰り道
on the way home
何だって話せる
We can talk about anything
親友の女の子
My best girl friend
スポーツ万能で
Good at sports
勉強もできて
and good at studying too
女子力マックスで
With maxed-out femininity
どこにでもある
It happens everywhere
よくあること
A common story
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she said...
「あのね、実は私、好きな人がいるの」って
"Hey, actually, there's someone I like."
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形　三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で　一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance collapses
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
A romance flag like a cliché manga
まさか自分も立てちゃうなんて
I can't believe I'd set one up myself
残念すぎます
It's just too unfortunate
三角形　三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって　なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category where "just kidding" won't cut it
恋と友情　ゆらゆら揺れてなんか
Love and friendship, swaying back and forth...
青春しちゃいます
I'm having a youth experience!
私、困っちゃいます
I'm in a bit of a bind!
乾杯で　お似合いすぎるわ、さては今回
A toast, you two look too good together. Now...
悔しいけど　どうかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's frustrating, but please, I hope that's not your true heart
っていうか既に　応援モード
Actually, I'm already in support mode
むしろ　すがすがしい
Actually, it feels refreshing
だけど彼女は　不思議な顔
But she had a mysterious look on her face
真剣なんだって
She said she was serious
「そうじゃなくて私、あなたが…」
"Not that, I... you..."
「好き。ごめん」って
"...like. Sorry."
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形　三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で　一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance collapses
私、あなた　彼女と私
Me, you, her and me
超絶複雑　百合展開は想定外です
This extremely complex yuri development is unexpected!
三角形　三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって　なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category where "just kidding" won't cut it
解けないパズル　与えたもうた
You gave me an unsolvable puzzle
神よ　うなっちゃいます
Oh God, I'm groaning!
私、悩んじゃいます
I'm worried!
あぁもう！すごいヤバイ！
Ah, geez! This is so bad!
見てよ！
Look!
きたけどさ、そういう意味じゃなくて…
It came, but I didn't mean it that way...
だって女の子同士だし…
I mean, we're both girls...
ねぇ神様、どうしたらいいの？
Hey God, what should I do?
私、どうしたいの！？
What do I want to do!?
HELP ME!
なんか変だ　愛に国境も歳も性別も関係ない
Something's strange. Love has no borders, age, or gender
けど　けど　けど
But, but, but...
三角形　三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で　一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance collapses
普通の恋　夢見てたのにな
I was dreaming of a normal love...
ノーマル捨てての私じゃ　ちょっと無理ゲーすぎます
Throwing away "normal" makes this life too much of a "kusoge"
三角形　三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
なんちゃって　なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category where "just kidding" won't cut it
彼女のこと　好きになれたら
If I could come to like her...
なんて　妄想しちゃいます
Just kidding, I'm deluding myself
私、どうかしてます
I'm going crazy
トライアングル・ドリーマー
Triangle Dreamer
好きだよ！
I love you!
わー！
Waah!
PHOENIX PRAYER
作詞・作曲：中村未来
Lyrics/Composition: Nakamura Miku
昏々と続くショート・ショート
A short-short that continues in a trance
喪失は絶対低度
Loss is at absolute zero
今夜、輪廻召喚、悲しみが
Tonight, reincarnation summon, sadness...
滾々と子守歌歌ってるよ
...is gushingly singing a lullaby
運命に猶予があるのならば
If there is a delay in fate
全てを賭けてみたいの
I want to try betting everything
あなたを守りたい
I want to protect you
どこまでも高く飛べるわ
I can fly high, anywhere
どこまでも強く強くなれるわ
I can become strong, anywhere
信じて、私に出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle of our meeting
切り拓くわ、不死鳥の炎解いて
I will cut through, unravelling the phoenix's flames
あなたの手
Your hand...
ブラック・ブラック、眼差し 泣きたくなるの
Black, black, that gaze makes me want to cry
フラッシュバック、フラッシュバック、振りほどけ
Flashback, flashback, shake it off
アセット、挑み続けろ
Asset, keep on challenging
飄々と佇むホット・ショット
An aloof-standing hot shot
私が必要でしょう？
You need me, don't you?
今夜、輪廻召喚、正しさが
Tonight, reincarnation summon, correctness...
それらしい最前線に押し出すよ
...pushes it to the likely front line
運命に猶予があるのならば
If there is a delay in fate
優しい世界をあげたい
I want to give you a kind world
あなたを包むわ
I will wrap you up
どこまでも速く射抜くわ
I will pierce through as fast as I can
どこまでも熱く熱く焦がすわ
I will burn as hot as I can
信じて、私に出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle of our meeting
切り拓くわ、不死鳥の炎解いて
I will cut through, unravelling the phoenix's flames
あなたの影
Your shadow...
ブラック・ブラック、彼方越し光を見せて
Black, black, show me the light from beyond
フラッシュバック、フラッシュバック、許さない
Flashback, flashback, I won't forgive
ビトレイ、進み続けろ
Betray, keep on moving forward
尽きるまで、側に居ると
That I'll be by your side until the end...
鼓動が速くて目眩がする
...my heart beats so fast it makes me dizzy
全て捧げる、もう決めたの
I'll offer everything, I've already decided
最後のチャンスだから離さない
It's the last chance, so I won't let go
あなたに燃ゆる
Burning within you...
未来の風、跨っていけ
...ride the wind of the future
どこまでも高く飛べるわ
I can fly high, anywhere
どこまでも強く強くなれるわ
I can become strong, anywhere
信じて、私に出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle of our meeting
闇夜も望めば輝に変えるから
Even the dark night will turn to brilliance if you wish
切り拓くわ、不死鳥の炎解いて
I will cut through, unravelling the phoenix's flames
あなたの手
Your hand...
ブラック・ブラック、眼差し 泣きたくなるの
Black, black, that gaze makes me want to cry
フラッシュバック、フラッシュバック、振りほどけ
Flashback, flashback, shake it off
アセット、挑み続けろ
Asset, keep on challenging
ブラック・ブラック、彼方越し光を見せて
Black, black, show me the light from beyond
フラッシュバック、フラッシュバック、許さない
Flashback, flashback, I won't forgive
ビトレイ、進み続けろ
Betray, keep on moving forward
ダイヤモンド クレバス
作詞：hal 作曲・編曲：菅野よう子
Diamond Crevasse
Lyrics: hal  Composition/Arrangement: Yoko Kanno
嗚呼...
Ah...
神様に恋をしていた頃は
Back when I was in love with God,
こんな別れが来るとは思ってなかったよ
I never thought a farewell like this would come.
嗚呼...
Ah...
もう二度と触れられないなら
If I can never touch you again,
せめて最後に、もう一度抱きしめて欲しかったよ
I wanted you to hold me at least one last time.
嗚呼...
Ah...
It's long long goodbye... さよなら、さよなら。
It's long long goodbye... Goodbye, goodbye.
何度だって、自分に無情に言い聞かせて
No matter how many times, I heartlessly tell myself.
手を振るのは優しさだよ、ね、嗚呼...
Waving goodbye is an act of kindness, right? Ah...
今、強さが欲しい
Now, I want strength.
あなたに出会い、さあ輝いて、私が生まれて
Meeting you, now I shine, and I am born.
愛すればこそ、愛あればこそ
Precisely because I love you, because love exists.
希望のない奇跡を待ってどうなるの
What happens if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙に滲む、星の瞬きは...
The twinkling of the stars, blurred by tears, is...
忘れないよ、あなたの温もりも
I won't forget, even your warmth.
その優しさも、すべて包んでくれた両手も
And that kindness, and your hands that held it all.
It's long long goodbye... さよなら、さよなら。
It's long long goodbye... Goodbye, goodbye.
愛おしい人、あなたがいたから歩いてこれた
My beloved, I could walk because you were here.
ひとりなんかじゃなかったよね、嗚呼...
I wasn't alone, was I? Ah...
今、答えが欲しい
Now, I want an answer.
燃えるような流星、捕まえて、火を灯して
Catch the burning shooting stars, light a fire.
愛していたい、愛されてたい
I want to keep loving, I want to be loved.
冷えた体、一つで世界はどうなるの
What happens to the world with just one cold body?
貼り続けてた、虚勢が溶けていく、long fall
The bluff I kept putting up melts away, long fall.
どうしてなんだろう
I wonder why it is so.
涙溢れて、止められない
Tears overflow, and I can't stop them.
あなたに出会い、さあ輝いて、私が生まれて
Meeting you, now I shine, and I am born.
愛すればこそ、愛あればこそ
Precisely because I love you, because love exists.
希望のない奇跡を待ってどうなるの
What happens if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙に滲む、星の瞬きは...
The twinkling of the stars, blurred by tears, is...
もし生まれ変わって、また巡り会うのなら
If I am reborn and we meet again,
その時もきっと、私を見つけ出して
then surely find me in that moment too.
もう二度と離さないで、捕まえてて
Don't ever let me go again, keep holding onto me.
ひとりじゃないと
That I am not alone
囁いてほしい
I want you to whisper
プラネット
Planet
Paradise Lost
作詞：畑 亜貴 / 作曲：菊田 大介
Lyrics: Aki Hata / Composition: Daisuke Kikuta
聖なる瞳が 痛みを映したら
If your holy eyes reflect pain
振り向いてごらん 情熱放つトリック
Look back and see, the trick that releases passion
崩れる足元 二人は戻れない
Our footing crumbles, the two of us cannot return
差し伸べた手をほどかないで
Do not let go of the hand I've reached out
消えるよまた 優しい日々が
Once again, the gentle days will fade away
思い出を汚すのは 許せない
I cannot forgive the tainting of memories
ここは裏切りの楽園 彷徨う心の果てに
This is the paradise of betrayal, at the end of a wandering heart
光を求めて 祈る言葉届け あなたに
Seeking light, let my prayer reach you
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
Imprisoned wings head toward the distant sky
信じたいよ私たち 孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we are not alone
分かり合える
Understanding each other
求め合える
Seeking each other
絆の中
Within our bond
離さない
Never let go
離れない
Never leave
始まるデスティニー
The beginning destiny
新たな願いに 鎖ほどけるとき
When the chains are loosened for a new wish
休ませてくれる 深い眠りに
Letting me rest in a deep sleep
僅かな希望が 私を強くする
A tiny bit of hope makes me stronger
温もりに触れてみたいから
Because I want to feel the warmth
蘇れば 儚き命
If resurrected, this fleeting life
繰り返す愛しさが 導いた
A recurring love has guided us
胸に泡沫の調べ 流れる世界の終わりに
A transient melody in my heart, at the end of the flowing world
諦めはしない 今がつなぐ明日 探そう
I won't give up, let's look for the tomorrow that the present connects to
引きちぎれ舞う羽は 未来の空にも向かう
Torn, dancing wings also head toward the sky of the future
忘れないで私たち 一つのクリスタル
Don't forget that we are one crystal
輝いて
Shine
壊れない
Indestructible
割れないのよ
It won't break
離さない
Never let go
離れない
Never leave
誓いのデスティニー
The destiny of our vow
Lost...
Paradise...
消えるよまた 優しい日々が
Once again, the gentle days will fade away
思い出を汚すのは 許せない
I cannot forgive the tainting of memories
ここは裏切りの楽園 彷徨う心の果てに
This is the paradise of betrayal, at the end of a wandering heart
光を求めて 祈る言葉届け あなたに
Seeking light, let my prayer reach you
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
Imprisoned wings head toward the distant sky
信じたいよ私たち 孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we are not alone
分かり合える
Understanding each other
求め合える
Seeking each other
絆の中
Within our bond
離さない
I won't let go
見つめて Paradise Lost
Staring at Paradise Lost
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow yeah
やっとみんな会えたね！
We finally all met!
Nonstop Nonstop Victory
GIRLS' LEGEND U
高鳴った全力走りたい
My heart throbbed, I want to run at full power
芝と砂と君の追い切りメニュー
Turf, sand, and your final training menu
叶え叶え声出せ叫べ
Grant it, grant it, raise your voice and scream
Wow...
それぜ！Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
That's it! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
高鳴った全力上がりたい
My heart throbbed, I want to go up at full power
譲れない夢の途中
In the middle of an unyielding dream
Wow...
始めよう ここから最高ストーリー
Let's start the best story from here
Oh oh oh...
ああ 焦がれる知恵
Ah, the wisdom I long for
語り合ったメモリー
The memories we talked about
もっとドキドキ もっとトキメキ
More pounding heart, more excitement
抑えられないたまんない
Can't hold back, it's unbearable
熱いハラハラが止まらなーい
This hot suspense won't stop
きっと
Surely
君と 走り競いゴール目指し
With you, racing towards the goal
はるか響け届けミュージック
Echo far away, reach us, music
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
Always, always, always, always, my feelings
夢がきっと叶うなら
If the dream will surely come true
あの日君に感じた 何かを信じて
Believing in something I felt for you that day
春も夏も秋も冬も声デカい 焦がれ走れ
Spring, summer, fall, winter, loud voices, long for it and run
あぁ 勝利へ
Ah, towards victory
Nonstop Nonstop Victory
高鳴った全力弾けたい
My heart throbbed, I want to burst at full power
大正解 決意 絆になった
The correct answer, determination, became a bond
感情 感情 本気で叫べ
Emotions, emotions, scream with all your might
Wow...
それぜ！Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
That's it! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
高鳴った全力笑いたい
My heart throbbed, I want to laugh at full power
カオスの中 真ん中
In the middle of the chaos
Wow...
リアルにここから上昇ストーリー
For real, a rising story from here
Oh oh oh...
駆け抜けた日々
The days we ran through
語り合ったグローリー
The glory we talked about
今応えたい 生きてると
Now I want to respond, that I'm alive
背中を押す声 熱くなーい
The voice pushing my back isn't it hot
夢は夢のまま終われない
A dream cannot end as just a dream
君と
With you
未来描きゴール目指し
Drawing the future, aiming for the goal
狙い定め掴めウィニング
Take aim and seize the winning
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
Always, always, always, always, my feelings
夢はきっと叶うから
Because the dream will surely come true
あの日君が鳴らした 涙も信じて
Believing even in the tears you shed that day
雨も風も雲も闇も声デカい 焦がれ走れ
Rain, wind, clouds, darkness, loud voices, long for it and run
あぁ 勝利へ
Ah, towards victory
揺るぎない覚悟決めて
With unwavering determination
一つ 二つ 共に綴る記録
One, two, records written together
背中に迫る迷い振り払え
Shake off the hesitation closing in behind
今の自分 追い越すだけ
Just overtaking my current self
勝ちたい
I want to win
君と勝ちたい！
I want to win with you!
夏も秋も冬も　越え願え　焦がれ走れ
Through summer, autumn, and winter, overcome, pray, yearn, and run
あぁ勝利へ
Ah, towards victory!
未来描き　望む目指し
Drawing the future, aiming for what we desire
狙い挑め　掴め　Winning
Target, challenge, and seize winning!
ずっと　ずっと　ずっと　想い
Always, always, always feeling
夢はきっと叶うから
Because dreams will surely come true
あの日君が流した
Believe in the tears
涙も信じて
You shed that day
雨も風も雲も闇も　越え願え　焦がれ走れ
Through rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, overcome, pray, yearn, and run
あぁ勝利へ
Ah, towards victory!
Don't stop! Non-stop to finish!
STARTING OVER
It's finally the true end.
I'm ready for... my destiny.
I'm ready for... STARTING OVER.
やっと幕を下ろせた　最後の瞬間まで
I finally lowered the curtain, until the very last moment
わたしは精一杯に　わたしをやりきった
I did my absolute best, I lived out my self to the fullest
終演の続きは　誰も知らなくていい
No one needs to know what follows after the final performance
涙を置いて　新しい旅に出よう
Leaving tears behind, let's set out on a new journey
熱狂はあなたを選ぶ　違う結末だっただけ
The fervor chooses you, it was just a different ending
同じ愛になれなかった Destiny
A destiny where we couldn't become the same love
これまでの全てを　差し出すような愛だった
It was a love that seemed to offer everything until now
世界の意味が変わるくらいに　肯定された気がしたんだ
I felt affirmed to the point where the meaning of the world changed
何気なさの中で　気づけた最初の奇跡が
The first miracle I noticed in the midst of casualness
あなたでよかった　わたしでよかった　心から思えたよ
I'm glad it was you, I'm glad it was me, I truly felt that from my heart
ずっと遠い未来も　ちゃんと覚えていよう
Let's remember even the far-off future properly
自分の抱きしめかた　明日の願いかた
How to embrace oneself, how to wish for tomorrow
あなたがいなくても　わたしの片隅で
Even without you, in a corner of my heart
優しい光　消えたりしないとわかる
I know that the gentle light will never fade
今はまだ手を振れるほど　道は別れたばかりで
For now, we've only just parted ways, enough to still wave hands
後ろ髪に風を感じながら
While feeling the wind against the back of my head
それまでの全てが　あなたに出会うためだった
Everything until then was all for the sake of meeting you
どの瞬間もムダじゃないこと　本当の意味で知れたから
Because I've learned in the truest sense that no moment was in vain
次の曲がり角も　自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next turn in the road as myself
いつかに繋がる　新しい一歩　信じて歩き出そう
Believe in the new step that leads to some day, and start walking
心から誰かを愛せた　あの日々は
Those days when I could love someone from the bottom of my heart
間違いなくわたしの Destiny Ah
Are undoubtedly my destiny, ah
これまでの全てが　新しい力をくれる
Everything until now gives me new strength
どの瞬間もムダじゃないなら　何が起きても大丈夫だから
If no moment is in vain, then everything will be alright, no matter what happens
次の物語も　自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next story as myself
いつかに繋がる　わたしのはじまり　信じて歩き出そう
Believe in my beginning that leads to some day, and start walking
Connecting to some day, my beginning, I'll walk out believing
再び幕は上がる
The curtain rises again
聞いていただいたのは、新曲の「STARTING OVER」でした！
The song you just heard was my new song, "STARTING OVER"!
はい、新年一発目、新曲の初披露というわけで...
Yes, the first new song reveal of the new year...
...ぬるっとね、新曲をやってしまったんですが...
...I kind of just slipped right into it...
平成感のある、えー、懐かしみの感じの楽曲を、こちらですね、歌わせていただいたんですけども...
It's a song with a Heisei-era feel, a nostalgic vibe, that I just performed for you...
このあと、この曲が、えー、24時から、あともう数時間後か。24時からですね...
And after this, at midnight—just a few hours from now—at midnight...
1月30日の24時から、配信、リリースされます！たくさん聞いてください！
...at midnight on January 30th, it will be released on streaming platforms! Please listen to it a lot!
今年もね、たくさんオリ曲、出していきたいです！
I want to release lots of original songs this year too!
そしてそしてもうMCが、ね、実は最後なので、ね、えっと...
And, and, this is actually the last MC section, so...
この配信のあとには、メンバー限定の配信もあるので、よろしくお願いします！
After this stream, there'll be a members-only stream, so look forward to that!
よし、よし、よし！グッズ紹介！
Alright, alright, alright! Merchandise introduction!
え、ここには同期のね、ポラボ、大集合ということで、えっと、ね、ら、ぼ、集まれー！
Since my Gen 5 mates, NePolabo, are all here... Ne, Ra, Bo, come on out!
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい、ちゃちゃちゃちゃ。初めて呼びました。どうも。
Yes, ta-da. First time calling them like that. Hello.
あれ？初だっけ？
Wait, is it the first time?
ポルカチャンネル初です。
It's our first time on Polka's channel.
ポルカチャンネル初だ！
First time on Polka's channel!
誕生日、誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ここまでが流れでございます、はい。
That's how it's gone so far, yes.
ずっと待ってたから。
We've been waiting for a while.
グッズをね、紹介させていただきたいと思います。皆様、失礼ながらの、リアクションなど、おのおの、とっていただいてくれると嬉しいです。
I'd like to introduce the merchandise now. Everyone, if you wouldn't mind, I'd love to hear your reactions.
ガヤ担当！
We're the hype squad!
というわけで、尾丸ポルカ誕生日記念グッズ2026、ラインナップはこちら！ドン！
Alright, so, here is the lineup for Omaru Polka's Birthday 2026 Memorial Merchandise! Boom!
というわけで、素晴らしい、今回もラインナップが揃っております。
And so, we have a wonderful lineup this time as well.
誕生日記念 2026
Birthday Memorial 2026
なんか、え、すごいけど... あれ？ちょっと... あれれ？あれれれれ？
Wait, it's amazing but... Huh? Just a second... Wait? What's going on?
持っていません！持っていませんね。
I'm not wearing it! I'm not wearing it.
というわけで、まず一つ一つ、ぼかしていきます。はい、まずは、こちら！
So, I'll go through them one by one. First, this!
はい、「ポルカのはじめての抱き枕カバー」になっております！
Yes, it's the "Polka's First Body Pillow Cover"!
ポルカのはじめての抱き枕カバー
Polka's First Body Pillow Cover
え、これ、ポルカさん、ちょっと、パンツ履いてませんか？
Wait, Polka, aren't you... not wearing pants?
あれ？丸出しじゃないですか？
Wait, are you exposed?
え、そんな、部屋着だよ！
Wait, it's just loungewear!
部屋着だよ。だって、ねねだって、こういう部屋着だもん。
It's loungewear. I mean, Nene wears loungewear like this too.
おーい、おいおいおい。人のチャンネルだからって、やりたい放題チャンネルして...
Hey, hey hey hey. Just because it's someone else's channel doesn't mean you can just do whatever...
いや、ほんま、シャツで寝たら、シワつくぞ。
Seriously, if you sleep in a shirt like that, it'll get wrinkled.
写真撮影用、かもしれないです。
It might be... just for the photoshoot.
というわけで、はじめて抱き枕カバー出します。表が通常衣装で、裏は「彼シャツ」になってます！
So, I'm releasing my first body pillow cover. The front is my usual outfit, and the back is the "boyfriend shirt" style!
彼シャツ！
Boyfriend shirt!
はい、ありがとうね、みんな！パセリ先生、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you everyone! Thank you, Parsley-sensei!
続きまして、ドン！こちら、「歴代衣装のポルカ、ランダムラバーストラップ」です！
Next, boom! This is the "Past Outfits Polka Random Rubber Strap"!
歴代衣装のポルカ ランダムラバーストラップ
Past Outfits Polka Random Rubber Strap
これまでの衣装のラバーストラップ。こちら、のいみみ先生に描いていただきました！
Rubber straps of my past outfits. These were illustrated by Noimimi-sensei!
え、めっちゃいいじゃん、これ。
Wait, these are really good.
どの衣装が出るかお楽しみに！ありがとうね、みんな。リアクション、本当に、100点満点です！
Look forward to seeing which outfit you get! Thank you, everyone. Your reactions are a perfect 100!
はい、続きまして、こちら、ドン！「どれもこれも宝物、思い出バインダー」！
Alright, next up, boom! The "Everything is a Treasure: Memory Binder"!
どれもこれも宝物 思い出バインダー
Everything is a Treasure: Memory Binder
いいですね、これ。
This is good.
最近みんなも特典で、チェキ風ブロマイドカード、出したりしてるから、そういうの入れたり...
Recently, everyone's been doing instax-style bromide cards as bonuses, so you can put those in...
あとはホロカも入るサイズになっていますので、ぜひぜひ、いろんな思い出しまってください！
...and it's also sized to fit Hololive Official Cards, so please use it to store all your memories!
「ポルカのしっぽキーホルダー」！
The "Polka's Tail Keychain"!
ポルカのしっぽキーホルダー
Polka's Tail Keychain
一周して流行ってるからね。ポルカのしっぽ型の、キーホルダー。
They're back in style now. It's a keychain in the shape of Polka's tail.
確かに確かに。平成レトロ、みたいな感じで...
True, true. It's got that Heisei-retro vibe...
平成レトロ、みたいな感じで、出ております。はい、こちらもつけてください。
It's being released with a Heisei-retro feel. Yes, please wear this too.
そしてボイスも出ます。ボイスはこちら、ジャン！
And we're also releasing voices. Here's the voice, ta-da!
ASMRボイスです！はい、えっと、まぁ、「彼シャツポルカの、『ただいま』の添い寝」という、ちょっと何か、タイトルも...
It's an ASMR voice! Yes, well, "Co-sleeping with Boyfriend-Shirt Polka: 'I'm Home'". The title is also a bit...
ASMRボイス「彼シャツポルカの、ただいまの添い寝。」
ASMR Voice: "Co-sleeping with Boyfriend-Shirt Polka: 'I'm Home'."
狙ってるじゃん！
You're totally aiming for that!
なんで今日同期呼んじゃったんだろうっていうの、一瞬思った今。恥ずかしくなってきた。
I just had a moment where I wondered why I invited my gen-mates today. I'm getting embarrassed.
うー、ここ今小学生になってる今。ガチガチ...
Ugh, everyone's acting like grade-schoolers now. Freezing up...
えーっと、添い寝ASMRというか、抱き枕カバーとイラストの関係がある、仕様になってます！
It's co-sleeping ASMR, and it's designed to go along with the illustration on the body pillow cover!
はい、皆様お待たせしました。フルセット購入特典になっております。こちら！
Yes, thank you for waiting. Here is the full set purchase bonus! This!
チェキ風ブロマイドカード。数量限定が直筆メッセージ、箔押し複製サインになっております！
The instax-style bromide card. The limited-quantity version has a handwritten message and a foil-stamped signature!
直筆メッセージ＆複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード
Instax-style bromide card with handwritten message & signature
通常が、箔押し複製サインと、メッセージ入りでございます！
The standard version has a foil-stamped signature and a message!
フルセット、ぜひぜひ、買っていただいた方には、特典ボイスとして...
For those who buy the full set, as a bonus voice...
「すやすやポルカの、添い寝ボイス」というか、え、エッ... 展開...
"Sleeping Soundly Polka's Co-sleeping Voice"... wait, whoa... Plot twist...
はーい、ということで、
All right, so,
フルセット購入特典、こちらのイラストはバセリさん、
the full set purchase bonus, the illustration is by Baseri-san,
一緒にね、寝ようね、みたいな感じの、なんかちょっとそういったボイスになってて、
it's an ASMR voice with a vibe like, 'Let's sleep together,'
こっちもASMRになってます。よろしくお願いします。
this one is also ASMR. Please check it out!
おおー！ よろしくお願いします！
Ohhh! We look forward to it!
恥ずかしいな、みんなとやるの、これ。
This is embarrassing, doing this with everyone.
なんか、えっちな女になってしまって、すみません。
I'm sorry for becoming such a... sultry woman.
いいじゃない、いいじゃない、
It's fine, it's fine!
新年もね、皆さん改めてこれからよろしくお願いします！
And with the new year, thank you all for your continued support!
よろしくお願いします！ バイバーイ！
Thank you for the support! Bye-bye!
ということで、今日はみんなで最後一緒に歌うために
So, I've called everyone here today
呼んできたということで、準備してきました。行ってみましょう！
so we can sing together at the end. We're ready, so let's go!
イェーイ！ いこー！
Yay! Let's go!
脚本は捨てちゃおうか　さしあたって焼き付けよ
Shall we throw away the script? Let's burn it in for the time being
アドリブの熱いパフォーマンス　屋根裏を飛び出して
A hot performance of ad-libs, jumping out of the attic
壮大なステージに響く　特別なストーリー
A special story echoing on a grand stage
瞼の裏には虹が描く
A rainbow draws behind my eyelids
星空のメモリー
Memory of the starry sky
等身大の愛を込めて
With all my life-sized love
想像を超える世界へ
To a world beyond imagination
誰も知らないでしょう？
No one knows, right?
Are You Ready?
どんな未来か見に行こうよ　なんて自由だ笑っちゃうよね
Let's go see what kind of future it is, it's so free it makes me laugh
ねぇホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, even further than the hologram
誰だって置いてかないよご覧　歓声が呼んでいる
I won't leave anyone behind, look, the cheers are calling
スラップからパッと照らす
Flashily illuminating from the slap
人生のスポットライト
The spotlight of life
薔薇色のプレミアショー
A rose-colored premier show
ここが特等席よ
This is the best seat
今日日ロマ遊びより　天気次第のエチュード
More than playing around these days, an étude depending on the weather
まるで絵物語　捕まえてよ
It's just like a picture story, catch me
待って！　ほら　待って！
Wait! Look, wait!
予想のできない展開に　ステージは揺れる
The stage shakes with unpredictable developments
特別なストーリー
A special story
耳を澄ましたら　月が踊る
If you listen closely, the moon dances
雨粒のハーモニー
Harmony of raindrops
浮かぶふわふわな空想　暴走？そこなしの本能！
A floating, fluffy fantasy. Runaway? Bottomless instinct!
すべて知りたいでしょう？
You want to know everything, right?
Hey Guys!　叫べ気分は最高！ (最高！)
Hey Guys! Shout, I feel the best! (The best!)
Come on!　もっと叫べ気分は最高！ (最高！)
Come on! Shout more, I feel the best! (The best!)
ポルカ終わるか？　ポルカ終わるか？
Is Polka ending? Is Polka ending?
ポルカ終わるか？　終わらない！
Is Polka ending? It's not ending!
It's Showtime!
繋いだ手離さないでなんてね
Don't let go of my hand, just kidding
どうしたって重たくなっちゃって困るわ
I'm in trouble because it's getting heavy no matter what
いつの日かエピローグを一緒に綴ろう
Let's write the epilogue together someday
きっと約束よ
I promise
Life Goes On!
どんな未来か見に行こうよ　なんて自由だ笑っちゃうよね
Let's go see what kind of future it is, it's so free it makes me laugh
ねぇホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, even further than the hologram
夢のような晴れ舞台に感情を馳せたら
When I set my emotions on a dream-like grand stage
スラップからパッと照らす
Flashily illuminating from the slap
人生のスポットライト
The spotlight of life
薔薇色のプレミアショー
A rose-colored premier show
どこまでだって添い遂げたい
I want to stay together forever
ここが特等席よ
This is the best seat
**出演**
**Cast**
尾丸ポルカ / AZKi / 百鬼あやめ
Omaru Polka / AZKi / Nakiri Ayame
大神ミオ / 不知火フレア / 宝鐘マリン
Ookami Mio / Shiranui Flare / Houshou Marine
桃鈴ねね / 雪花ラミィ / 獅白ぼたん / 鷹嶺ルイ / 風真いろは
Momosuzu Nene / Yukihana Lamy / Shishiro Botan / Takane Lui / Kazama Iroha
あんたにゃ　もったいない
I'm too good for you
あたいは本当　ナイスバディ・バディ・バディ
I really have a nice body, body, body
自分で　言うくらい
I say so myself
タダじゃない　じゃない　じゃない　(じゃない！ Ah ha!)
It's not free, not free, not free (Not free! Ah ha!)
熱けりゃ　冷ませばいい
If it's hot, just cool it down
寂しけりゃ　Everybody Body Body
If you're lonely, everybody body body
誰にも　わからない
Nobody knows
恋愛って　いつ火がつくのか
When the spark of love will ignite
ダイナマイト　恋はダイナマイト　恋はダイナマイト
Dynamite, love is dynamite, love is dynamite
どんなに　不景気だって　恋はインフレーション
No matter how bad the recession, love is inflation
こんなに　優しくされちゃ　みだら
Being treated so kindly makes me feel... lewd
明るい　未来に
Towards a bright future
就職希望だわ
I want to apply for a job
Glitter of Love
日本の未来は
Japan's future is...
世界がうらやむ
...the envy of the world
恋をしようじゃないか
Let's fall in love
Dance!　Dancin' all of the night
なんだか　物足りない
Somehow, it's not enough
どこに立って　愛してほしいわ
Wherever I stand, I want to be loved
自分で　伝えるの
To tell you myself...
恥ずかしい　じゃない　じゃない　(ない！ Wow!)
...is embarrassing, isn't it? (Isn't it! Wow!)
いっそ　二人がいい
Actually, the two of us would be better
憧れよ　Everybody Body Body
It's a longing, everybody body body
誰もが　気づいてない
Nobody has realized
恋愛って　夢の落とし穴
That love is a pitfall of dreams
ミステリー　恋はミステリー　恋はミステリー
Mystery, love is a mystery, love is a mystery
そんなの　不自然だって　恋のインサイダー
Even if they say it's unnatural, it's a love insider
それでも　上手にされちゃ　ラ・ワ・ワ
Even so, being treated skillfully, la-wa-wa
幸せ　来る日も
Happiness, even on coming days
キャンセル待ちだわ
I'm on the waiting list
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile is...
世界がうらやむ
...the envy of the world
夢があるじゃないか
There is a dream, isn't there?
Dance!　Dancin' all of the night
Love!　Love Machine!
Love!　Love Station!
Love!　Love Factory!
Love!　Love is so wonderful!
企画・構成・総合演出：尾丸ポルカ
Planning, Construction, General Production: Omaru Polka
Special Thanks
座員のみんな / 見てくれたすべての皆様
All the Zain / Everyone who watched
日本の未来は
Japan's future is...
世界がうらやむ
...the envy of the world
恋をしようじゃないか
Let's fall in love
Dance!　Dancin' all of the night
あんたも　あたいも
You and me too
みんなも　社長さんも
Everyone and the boss too
Dance!　Dancin' all of the night
LOVEマシーン！
LOVE Machine!
今日は主役だ！！ まだまだ かがやく場所へ つれていくぜ！！ I LOVE YOU♥
I'm the star today!! I'll keep taking you to shining places!! I LOVE YOU♥
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026 Glitter of Love
#OmaruPolkaBirthday2026 Glitter of Love
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
新曲のお披露目あり！ 「Glitter of Love」
#OmaruPolkaBirthday2026
New song reveal included! "Glitter of Love"
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト 10 名
1/30 21:00〜
Most guests in a Polka live yet: 10 Hololive members
Jan 30, 21:00~